q1media.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Q1Media Inc

Q1Media, Inc. takes privacy concerns seriously and we strive to ensure that our privacy policy improves the services we provide to advertisers, publishers, and web users in general.

Q1MEDIA, INC. PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy was last modified on 5/9/2016

This Privacy Policy concerns two different types of users of our services. The first are Internet users who go to a website where our advertising technology is used. The second are publishers (i.e., website owners) and advertisers who register with us via the Internet. The type of information we gather with respect to a web user who is delivered advertising through our advertising technology versus someone who registers with our site is very different. Accordingly, this policy sets forth, in separate sections, our policies with respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of information we obtain from these two different types of users and a third section which is applicable to both types of users, including those visiting our site to view this privacy policy. For purposes of understanding the information that we collect, it is important at the outset to discuss two different types of information that can be obtained from Internet users. Personally Identifiable Information for purposes of this Privacy Policy refers to information that identifies you personally including your name, email address, mailing address, or phone number. This includes any type of information that identifies who you are, rather than an anonymous profile. Anonymous Information includes information that does not personally identify you. Examples include the IP Address of the computer used, web pages you have viewed, search queries, ads you have viewed, date and time of your actions, the location at which you accessed a web page, domain type, and the responses you have made to advertisements. We collect this type of information through technologies that do not identify you as an individual and such information is never associated with your Personally Identifiable Information, even if we have Personally Identifiable Information related to you.

SECTION ONE – INTERNET INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM INTERNET USERS

This section sets out the type of information we obtain from Internet users who happen upon a website that uses our advertising technology. It is important you know that we do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information from such users. We and/or third party advertising technology vendors may use different types of technologies to collect this type of information including cookies. You may elect to not allow us to use anonymous data by following the Opt-Out procedures set forth in the “Option to Opt Out.” Cookies. Q1Media uses “cookies” which are small text files that are transferred to your computer through your web browser by a site or its service provider to capture and remember certain information. Through our proprietary advertising technology we place these anonymous cookie identifiers on your web browser so that we can collect data about your online movements without ever knowing exactly who you are. We collect and analyze your data under an anonymous and randomly assigned name such as “user45,” and each time you use a different browser, a different computer, or a mobile device’s browser you get a different anonymous identifier such as “user97” or “user805.” The Q1Media cookie does not harm your computer or mobile device in any way or provide us with any information about your personal identity. The cookie is not spyware or adware, which are installed to monitor Internet and general computer activity. Most Web browsers have settings so that the browser can refuse cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent.

Third Party Information.

Q1Media partners with third parties who collect information from your Web browser, through “web beacons,” “gif tags,” and the like. This information can include data concerning requests received which is obtained by the web browser. Examples of this type of information include your web browser type, the websites that you visited just before or just after a website displaying our ad or ads, and the dates and times that you visit a website with our ads. The third party may receive information when you interact with our ads by clicking on the ad or associating them with a social media platform, such as Facebook or Twitter. The information a third party may receive from such interaction includes the specific ad clicked on and the specific web page on which the ad is placed. Q1Media may receive information regarding the frequency with which specific ads are displayed to a user. The third party may receive information regarding the frequency with which specific ads are displayed to a user and information regarding click-throughs, i.e., your clicking to a website linked to the ad or links that you share or receive from third parties related to those ads.

HOW DO WE USE INTERNET USER INFORMATION?

The Anonymous Information we gather from Internet users helps us learn how to best provide ad services that are tailored to the needs and interests of a specific anonymous user. In your case, this means that the information obtained anonymously helps us find patterns that allow us better to respond to your needs and interests. For instance, if we have Anonymous Information that a user recently searched for “Hawaii,” we may use that information to decide to display an advertisement for airfare to Hawaii when that user visits a website using Q1Media ads. We also use the information to improve our ads’ effectiveness and not over display the same ad to users.

You may also get cookies from our affiliates and business partners if you use the links on our Site to reach their respective web sites. The use of advertising cookies sent by such third party web servers is standard in the Internet industry. Q1Media does not control these cookies.

DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?

Anonymous Information: Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. We share such Anonymous Information with our partners, advertisers, and other third parties at our discretion. Compliance with the Law: We may release your information when we believe in good faith that release is appropriate to (a) comply with the law; (b) respond to subpoenas, warrants, or other governmental orders; or (c) protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety.

We receive information about consumers from third parties to enable targeted advertising on the website(s) and application(s) that we support. The collection and use of that data is governed by the privacy policy and legal terms of the data collector and the website using the data; it is not governed by Q1Media.

OPTION TO OPT OUT

To opt out of these third party cookies, you may visit the following partner websites:

OPT OUT LINK SECTION TWO – CONCERNING THOSE WHO REGISTER WITH US FOR OUR SERVICES

If you register as a publisher on our website, we will collect from you Personally Identifiable Information, including your name, address, email address, phone number, fax number, and your website URL. We use this information in a number of ways, including potentially or actually establishing a business relationship with you; offering and improving customer service (your information helps us more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs); and in processing transactions. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the Personally Identifiable Information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. As a publisher we appreciate your feedback about our services and website. Your Personally Identifiable Information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any unassociated third parties without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. However, in the event of a merger or sale of Q1Media, we reserve the right to transfer or assign your Personally Identifiable Information (and the right to use it), to the merged, purchasing, or subsequent entity that takes over our advertising services for which you have registered and we will require such successor entity to honor this Privacy Policy In addition, we may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. Examples of such disclosures include sending email, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments (including credit card payments), and providing customer service. We reserve the right to share some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information with any future parent companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, “Affiliates”). Upon sharing some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information with these Affiliates, we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

HOW WE PROTECT PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

Q1Media utilizes a variety of physical, electronic, and managerial security measures to maintain the safety of your Personally Identifiable Information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. However, no company, including Q1Media, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

CHANGES TO PERSONAL INFORMATION

Q1Media displays certain information given during the creation and registration of your account as a publisher. If you wish to change your email address or other contact information, you may login to your Q1Media account to do so, or contact us at the address or phone number below.

SECTION THREE – POLICIES RELATING TO BOTH TYPES OF USERS USERS OF OUR SITE

If you are reading this Privacy Policy then it is likely that you have visited our site. If that is the case, we will likely have placed an anonymous cookie on your web browser. This is the type of cookie we describe above under the section above entitled “INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM INTERNET USERS – Cookie”. We use these cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (COPPA) COMPLIANCE

Q1Media regards issues of children’s privacy with the utmost sensitivity and seriousness. To our knowledge, we are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA. We do not knowingly collect information from anyone under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly place ads on websites directed to children under the age of 13 or on web pages that are directed to children under the age of 13 that are on general websites. Our website, products, and services are all directed to and developed for people who are at least 13 years old or older. If you are a parent or guardian and believe that your child has provided personal information to Q1Media, please advise us immediately so that we can remove the data.

THIS SITE IS FOR UNITED STATES USERS

The hosting of this site is done in the United States and it is intended for users located in the United States. If you are outside of the United States please note that the laws of your jurisdiction regarding data collection and tracking may vary with the laws of the United States. By providing us with your Personally Identifiable Information you are consenting to its use by us.

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy page and update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Disputes arising under the Privacy Policy will be resolved in accordance with the latest version of the Privacy Policy for which we have obtained your consent. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy frequently in order to stay informed of the latest modifications.

EFFECTIVE DATE

CONTACTING US If there are any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below.  
www.q1media.com  
11401 Century Oaks Terrace Austin, TX Suite 470 United States  
privacy@q1media.com  
512-388-2300
